Hi guys, so in this video you are going to see
iPartner Pro.  This
is an app from ICIC Lamborgh.  With this you
can earn by taking general insurance.  So I am going to
show the complete review of the apps.  Don't
skip anywhere.  What all is the app
providing?  And finally,
what is the feedback from people who have used the apps?  What is their review?  So
you will know whether you should use the app or
not.  Before starting, if
you have not yet subscribed to the MB Talkies channel, please
like the video and
subscribe to the channel.
Click on the bell icon.  So let's start.
My name is Mohammad Irfan.  You are watching
NB Talkies channel.  I p This is
apps from the house of ICIC LBD Channel Insurance.
Its rating in Play Store is 4.4 1K reviews. I will
show you the review in the ending.  Be
sure to check reviews before using the apps.   The
app is 35 MB in size.  1 lakh plus people have
downloaded it.  So you can see that you can
become a partner.  You can run.  You can start your
own business in your own time without any
spending etc.  So
you can earn by joining.  Apart from this,
become your own boss.  You can sow your own.
Everything is under control here.  You can earn commissions by selling this general
insurance, car insurance, two wheeler
insurance etc.
So you can see that you can become an
Insurance Surgeon of ICIC LB with i
partner pro Mobile Life and what you
can do with it is you get an exciting career
opportunity to earn Insurance
Awaits
you i partner pro is the perfect insurance
sales session for insurance and post
agent. You can generate income from ICIC LB
through this simple
and powerful app. It helps you
in becoming an Insurance Agent. You
can start with zero investment and earn
up to Rs.85 per month commission in
insurance business with i partner Pro.
No insurance experience is required.  You don't
need it.  You just have to download the app
and go through some basic training
and verification steps.  You can start this
business as soon as the application is
verified.  So Words on the Apps.
What options will you get in the app?  So first of all
you can see Words on the Apps.
Once you download the app, you will be
required to self-register.
You have to verify the documents and complete
15 hours of training on Monday.
This is mandatory from IRDA.
This app configures you with the
required course material. You can become a
satisfied point of sale, that is, post is
called point of sale person post.
Once your training is complete, your
insurance will be processed as an exam and executed.
Your agreement will be done.
You are ready to sell insurance.
After this, what you have to do
is sell through the app. This is a pretty
straight forward app.  You can generate this.
Instant Qs means what will be the cost of the sale
, how much premium etc. for a
product available in the app, one the customer
pays premium.  The customer will pay a premium.
The policy will be issued.  You will get it instantly.
You do not need to visit the branch.
You will not have to monitor paperwork etc.  It's
all apps.  You will get the commission.  You
can see what
is more.  You want be lots and along with you are
figure out how to make insurance sales how
you have to.
You will get a dedicated ICICI LB relationship manager.
Provides necessary sales
support so you can grow your insurance
business online and move you into a
trusted one.  Friendly insurance advisor
to your customer.  You want friendly insurance
advice.  You can get insurance.
Once you start selling
you will start earning commission.  It will start and you will
get the commission.  Now your
earnings will be transferred to your bank account which you will
provide. The more you sell in the app, the
more you will
earn.  So what makes the iPro awesome
?  So along with the training material
you get resources.  You need to
qualify any advisor to generate
instant quotes for motor insurance
policies.  Also helps you sell
instant policies without paperwork and
branch visits.  There is no need to do any brand business.
Helps you as an insurance
agent earn commission quickly and easily
through digital sales.  You
can download the app and sign up to start
today.  So let me show you in detail the manner, bug fixes, access and what else is there in the new app.  So do
n't skip this from anywhere.  1 lakh plus people have
downloaded it.  The app is 35.34 MB.  The
rating is 4.4 out of five showing in the Play Store.
So the first light
they gave is on the dashboard it shows
policies are due for renewable but when
you click on the renew it shows nothing not able
to download the quotation as well as to go back
to the desktop.  Meaning the policy is being
issued for renewal but is not getting renewed.
Lovely from the apps motor section is removed
just vanish i can only see it lately sorry lately
from the apps so vanish ho ja raha hai motor
section etc app not work very well dekh sakte ho
not user friendly very login
and issue etc aa raha hai app not very well
back office support is zero please don't join
ICIC LB SM so negative feedback is their two
five star dekh sakte ho for the past few
month i have realized on iPartner Pro to
revolutionize my task management its user
friendly interface similarly integrated
and powerful feature have become impossible for
my daily ex operation and business detail.
I can't see my work revolution with
audit.  I highly recommended it for
everyone who asks for efficient tools.   The
second one is also five star.  I have been
using iPartner Pro for the past three
months.  And it is truly transforming the way I
manage the task. The user-friendly interface,
simple integrations, and reverse features make it the perfect
NSSL tool for my daily login and
business daily.  I Can't Images My Work
Without It Highly Recommended Feel free to
customize it with this specific detail
about the appreciation and your personal business
details.  So it is also five star.  You can see that there is
negative as well as positive feedback.
All types of feedback are available in this.  There is
one star as well as five star.
In between, you can see reviews of all types 2, 3, 4,
I have shown you some of them in this video.
You have to read more details by
going to Play Store and you have to read
in details and join.   If
you feel like joining, you can join.
So first of all check the reviews of all of them thoroughly.   If
you do not understand any step in this video, you
can tell us by commenting in the comment box below.  If
you have not yet subscribed to MB Topic channel, please
subscribe to the channel by liking the video.
Click on the bell icon and share this
video as much as possible on WhatsApp,
social media, friend circle and
wherever.  Thanks for
watching the video guys.